3D Meshes.
3D メッシュについて、みてきます。
Scenes in Unity are created by
Unity におけるシーンは
using 3D or polygonal meshes.
3D 、またはポリゴン メッシュにより作成されています。
Polygonal meshes are the underpinnings
ポリゴン メッシュは Unity で作成されるゲームを
of all games made in Unity.
支えるものです。
Whether it's a simple 2D game where the
それがキャラクターが簡単な平面に
characters are attached to a simple plane,
アタッチされたシンプルな 2D ゲームであろうと、
a complex particle system full of sprites,
スプライトだらけの複雑なパーティクルシステムであろうと、
or a full 3D game with animated characters -
または、アニメーションつきキャラクターのフル 3D のゲームであろうと、
that game will use meshes.
ゲームはメッシュを使用します。
All objects in our game, from a simple
ゲームにおける全てのオブジェクトは、
quad or basic plane, to a complex
簡単な四角形でも基本的な平面でも、
3D character or environmental geometry
複雑な 3D キャラクターまたは環境におけるオブジェクトでも、
will be a polygonal mesh.
ポリゴン メッシュです。
Polygonal meshes, or simply meshes
ポリゴン メッシュ、あるいはシンプルなメッシュは
are created from very simple basic elements.
とても基本的な要素から作成されます。
Points and lines.
それは点と線です。
The points are called Vertices
点は Vertices （頂点）または
or Verts for short.
略して Verts と呼ばれます。
A single point is a Vertex.
ひとつの頂点は Vertex と呼びます。
These define a point in 3D space.
これらは 3D 空間の点を定義します。
Between these points lines are drawn.
これらの点の間に線が描画されｍさう。
These lines are called Edges.
これらの線はエッジと呼ばれます。
The edges create something called a Polygon.
これらのエッジがポリゴンと呼ばれるものを形成します。
which in Unity will be a triangle.
Unity の場合は、三角形から構成されます。
These polygons define the mesh of our object.
これらのポリゴンはオブジェクトのメッシュを定義します。
The meshes used in Unity
Unity で使用されるメッシュは
are not created in Unity.
Unity の中で作成されるわけではありません。
With the exception of the basic primitive
例外は基本的な原始図形（プリミティブ）であり、
shapes which are built in to Unity
これらは Unity にあらかじめビルトインされていて
all of the meshes that we will be using
使用する全てのメッシュは
need to be created in an external
外部のメッシュ モデリング アプリケーションを使用して
mesh modelling application.
作成する必要があります。
These mesh models, either created or
これらのメッシュモデル、
purchased will need to be imported in to
作成または購入されたものは
Unity for use in our scenes.
Unity にインポートしてシーンで使用することをｋ考えて生きます。
See the Mesh Import lesson linked below.
メッシュのインポートに関するレッスンも参照して下さい。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)